

ABDUL MANAF UI UX DESIGNER

www.abdulmanaf.com

CONTACT

Abu Dhabi,UAE abdulmanaf006@gmail.com +971 525715447

Portfolio: https://abdulmanaf.live-website.com

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe Animate Figma Adobe XD Miro Html & css **JavaScript** Jquery

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science, Bharathiar University,India 2007-2010

CERTIFICATIONS

Diploma in Web Graphic Animation Arena Multimedia Bangalore India [2010 - 2011]

SUMMARY

An accomplished technical professional, in Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma and Frontend Developing HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and ¡Query with an experience of 10+ years.

Web application UI/UX for projects over the span of years and live application testing and support based in Finance and Accounting, E-assets and Time and Attendance for the Government Clients.

Bringing a designer's concept to life with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query Production, modification, and maintenance of websites and web application user interfaces and Kiosk Interfaces Use latest front-end frameworks to develop user-friendly web pages.

Experience in Mobile Applications UI/UX Designs

Developing, supporting, testing and troubleshooting production applications (live applications)

Experience in requirement analysis, documentation of requirements

EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer and FrontEnd Developer (MAR 2023 - Present)

Zayed Higher Organization for People of Determination - Abu Dhabi, UAE

Responsibilities: . As a UX/UI Designer, i will play a crucial role in understanding user needs, designing intuitive interfaces, and ensuring that our digital products are visually appealing and user-friendly, and collaborate closely with cross-functional teams to create designs that enhance user satisfaction and drive business success. User Experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery Production, modification, and maintenance of websites and web application user interfaces

UI/UX Designer and FrontEnd Developer (SEP 2021 - FEB 2023) Rainmaking Ventures Technology LTD - Dubai, UAE

Responsibilities: Overseeing design projects from conception to delivery, Working closely with the Head of Growth to design visual assets that support marketing and business development campaigns, Working alongside the Product and Development teams of our Ventures to translate business requirements and user needs into compelling design solutions. Developing the brand identity of Ventures across digital and off-line channels (from logo to marketing collaterals, websites, and mobile apps) Develop User interfaces for Modern Rich Internet Applications with the latest Front End Technologies, Participating in reviews, stand-ups of Product Backlog, Sprints, and Business Requirements, Developing pixel-perfect web UI that matches designs and business require-

UI/UX Designer (OCT 2015 - AUG 2021)

Smart Vision for Information's Systems - Abu Dhabi, UAE

Bringing a designer's concept to life User Interface design, Prototyping, visual and graphic designs, flow diagrams, storyboards, site maps, style guides, User Experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query Production, modification, and maintenance of websites and web application user interfaces and Kiosk Interfaces Use latest front-end frameworks to develop user-friendly web pages Developing, supporting and troubleshooting production application.

UI/UX Designer (AUG 2013 - JUL 2015)

Craft LLC - Abu Dhabi, UAE

Responsibilities: Bringing a designer's concept to life with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Designing web pages, newsletters, graphic Icons. Logo's Design, Flyer Design and Graphics Design

Ecommerce website upations and Designed weekly email promotions sent to over all users and redesigned ads for various platforms (Facebook, Google, etc.)

PERSONAL INFO

D.O.B: 06 Nov 1989 Religion:Islam Marital Status: Married Nationality: India